JORGE HERNANDEZ

FRONT END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 951 379 8533

Moreno Valley, CA

in www.linkedin.com/in/jorgekwu

PROFILE

Hello World. I was an assistant English professor and teacher in South Korea for 9 years. About a year ago, I decided that I wanted to drastically change my career and work on a team building responsive, modern, and clean web applications that people around the world can use.

EDUCATION

MA TESOL Azusa Pacific University 2011 - 2013

BA ENGLISH UC Riverside 2004 - 2008

SKILLS

WordPress/Plugins

Social media management

Git basics

JavaScript basics

HTML 5

CSS (flexbox, grid)

UI/UX design basics

Visual Studio Code

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Patio Furniture Plus - Company Website and Catalog

http://fzn.cfx.mybluehost.me/ - In Progress
Web Developer | Oct 2020 - Present
Customized WordPress theme for company site

- WordPress plugins: analytics, newsletter, layout customization
- Curated social media: Instagram @patiofurnitureplus, Facebook Business Suite

Personal Page

www.jorgesportfoliopage.com | 2020

Responsive landing page with a simple design. Basic form submission and hamburger menu included. Created to showcase front end skills

- Responsive design
- HTML, CSS, and a bit of JavaScript
- · Form submission through Netlify

Assistant Professor

Kwangwoon University, Seoul, Korea | 2015 - 2020 English language instruction ranging from conversational skills to business communication at the university level

- Achieved high student evaluation: 4.89/5
- Strong reputation of valuable courses
- One semester of online instruction